Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
What?
When?
Yeah. okay. Okay.
Babe? You okay?
Babe. are you alright?
Warren. Derek. and Joanne
were killed last night.
Oh. my God.
And Sam's missing.
Do you know who did it?
Same crew.
It has to be.
Stay here.
Wyatt. where's
your water bottle?
Come on. Wyatt. we don't
wanna miss the bus again.
-Can I have Pop-Tarts?
-Here's your lunch box.
Come on. we don't
wanna be late.
Mornin'.
-Hey. Dad.
-Morning. fart face.
What are you still doing home?
I. uh...
I called out of work.
-Throat's all scratchy.
-Hey. Harper needs $25.
What for?
Father-daughter dance
is Thursday night.
School's bringing in pizzas.
We don't have to go.
-Dad. I don't even really wanna go.
-Hell yes. we're going.
I... I've been looking
forward to that.
Definitely goin'.
I'm gonna take a nap.
Aleah and Lizzie. drive
around the neighborhood
and see if any door
cams got anything.
Grasso and I will go talk
to Kenny Pollard's fiancée.
-Circle back here after?
-No. no. it's too chaotic.
Let's meet at base camp.
-Lizzie?
-Uh-huh?
Assign an analyst
to vet the tips.
Uh. any confirmed
ones come through.
have NCMEC patch them
through back to us.
Copy.
Anything?
Hasn't gotten back to me yet.
Jesus fuckin' Christ.
-Hey.
-There wasn't supposed to be
-no fuckin' kid in that house. man.
-Hey. hey. hey. hey.
-Hey. hey.
-There wasn't supposed to be no fuckin' kid.
Hey. look at me. look
at me. look at me.
Look at me.
-I keep seeing their faces.
-Me too.
-Blood all over.
Hey.
How long we been friends?
Hundred years?
Have I always found
a way out of things?
We never did anything
like this. We never...
That's not what I asked.
Have I always found a way out?
What do I always say?
Everything happens for a reason.
Robbie. we killed those people.
We got Peaches killed.
There ain't no fuckin' reason.
Then. we're gonna make one.
We're gonna make
a fuckin' reason.
-The fuck? Where's the cash?
-Shh. No. No.
Where's the fuckin' money?
Don't touch.
Looks like fentanyl.
Still wrapped.
What's that mean.
"still wrapped"?
Right over the border.
-Uncut.
-It's supposed to be cash.
The fuck are we
gonna do with this?
If it's what I think it is.
worth a hell of a
lot more than cash.
I'm kind of hungry.
Go back inside and. uh.
I'll be right there.
What are we gonna do with him?
Robbie. he's seen our faces.
He's been inside your house.
Go down to Monmouth Street.
Buy some test strips.
What for?
Make sure it's pure. We
gotta sell this shit.
Hey. Good mornin'.
What do you normally
eat for breakfast?
Mm. I like pancakes.
Alright. Pancakes
it is. Come on.
What's your name again?
Robbie.
Are those chickens?
-Yeah.
-Can I see them?
Come here.
You see?
-Can I pet them?
-Yeah.
Here. look. look.
You see the one
with the black feathers
that's kind of in the middle?
-Yeah.
-That one's Gertie.
She's nice. she'll
let you pet her.
I wish humans could
talk to animals.
-"Ec-specially" deer.
-Why deer?
What do you wanna say
to deer specifically?
I'd tell them not
to cross the street
and to stay in the forest.
'Cause a lot of deer die
trying to cross the street.
Yeah. Yeah.
How long do I have to stay here?
Um...
Uh. we'll see. Not too
long. I don't think.
Your. um... your
parents said a few days.
Someone was sick. Is there
someone in your family
that hadn't been
feeling too hot?
My grandmother.
That's it. That's
what they said it was.
They said. um. that they got
a call late at night that...
you know. your grandmother
was feeling sick. and. um...
How do you know my mom and dad?
Um...
Uh. my brother.
he actually worked with your
father and his friends...
-Hey.
...a long time ago.
before you were born.
How do you like your pancakes?
Fluffy or crispy?
Fluffy.
Definitely fluffy.
Give me a sec.
So...
What do we know
about the other body
found in Nance's house?
The one from their crew?
Still waitin' on my contacts.
How the fuck did they
know about the shipment?
-No word back on Sam yet?
-No.
The kid's dead.
They took him just
to fuck with us.
Six feet in the dirt somewhere.
I'm sorry. Jay.
I'm just upset.
Call an emergency
church meeting.
Bring everyone.
Good morning.
FBI special agent Tom Brandis.
David. Kaylee's father.
TFO Anthony Grasso.
So. uh. this must have been
a pretty overwhelming
day for you. huh. Kaylee?
I know the police have
questioned you already.
but it's very
important that we know
who Peaches went
out with last night.
It's not that I don't remember.
I just. like. literally haven't
met any of his friends yet.
We met online. I just moved here
from Ohio a few weeks ago.
This may be very
difficult to hear. but...
Peaches was killed
during a home invasion.
and it appears as
though he was involved
-with the incident.
-In the invading?
Yes.
And it's not the only incident
-he was involved in.
-Jesus Christ. I fucking knew
he was a piece of shit the
moment I set eyes on him.
-And I said. "Kaylee Grace Prater..."
-Would you stop. please?
"...this kid is a
full-on nothing."
-I told you from the get-go...
-Dad. stop!
-Could you just not right now. please?
-...you should not be with him.
Okay. my... I just
lost my soul mate.
We... we had plans.
-and now I...
-Hey. okay. Okay.
Honey. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. Mm-hmm.
Kaylee?
Several other people were
killed inside the home.
Alright. right now. a
six-year-old boy is missing.
No. you're... you're not...
-You think...
-It's not that we...
-You think Peaches did that? No.
-It's not that we think. Kaylee.
We know Peaches was
a part of this crew.
-No. that's... no.
-I'm sorry.
No. I don't think I
like you two very much.
-I understand.
-No.
-Kaylee. listen to me.
-No. No.
Kaylee...
...it's very important
that we know...
-No!
-...who his work friends were
so that we could
find this little boy.
I think you two should leave.
-Do chickens have dreams?
-Hm.
I never really
thought about that.
I bet they do.
I bet they dream of big farms.
Yeah. that makes sense.
Can't find my glasses. Could
you... would you mind...
Want me to... I'll read
it. I'll read it for you.
It's. uh. uh. from Sara.
"Heavy rain here.
Flight delayed.
Scheduled to land...
land at 4:15 now."
Okay.
My daughter's coming in
from Chicago this afternoon.
Oh. that'll be nice. right?
Little... little
quality family time?
Mm-hmm.
How long have you
been with the FBI?
Uh. officially since '03.
but I was. uh.
assisting the Bureau
for many years before that
as a... as a chaplain.
A chaplain like a...
like a... like a...
-Like a priest.
-You're fuckin' with me.
Mm. no. I'm not
fuckin' with you.
I don't think people lie about
being a priest very much.
-especially these days. Grasso.
-Yeah. but so help me connect the dots.
I mean. how does a... how does a
priest end up working for the FBI?
Uh. I was a volunteer on their
crisis intervention team.
Um. they'd fly
clergy out with them
when they went to
mass casualty events.
-Columbine. Oklahoma City.
-Yeah. Yeah.
So. uh. yeah. that's where I
met my supervisor. Kathleen.
And when I left the priesthood
and married my wife.
she. uh. she pulled some strings
and got me into Quantico.
What were they
expecting a priest to do
at these mass casualty events?
Sprinkle some holy
water or. uh...
Counsel.
Yeah. when things
go terribly wrong.
people want to know
why God let it happen.
Huh.
-What?
-Ah. Yeah. man. well...
Well. it's just... so I grew
up. uh. Catholic. and my mother.
she had three jobs and never
took a shift on Sunday.
Sundays was for church.
I mean. she would... she
would drag me and my sister
to Immaculate Heart
for 7 a.m. mass.
quiz us on the
readings afterwards.
I mean. every
Sunday for 18 years.
And. um. and forgive me. Father.
but. um. you know. none of it
ever made an ounce of sense to me.
I mean. forget the Trinity
and the Transfiguration.
Those are... those
are. you know.
Just what I wanna know
is... is that. you know.
why God gives a shit if we
eat meat on Fridays. you know?
-Right?
-Right.
I mean. what. is
the Catholic church
colluding with Papa
John's or something?
I don't know. maybe we
should get the Bureau
-to look into that for us.
-Yeah. please do. please do.
I'd like to enjoy a
slice of pepperoni
without the threat
of eternal damnation.
This is literally
the third time
she's asked me if it's a weave.
I don't know. why don't you
ask her if her hair's a weave?
Actually. don't say that.
I'm gonna get in trouble.
I love those. by the way.
Aren't they amazing?
So?
What's new at home?
Not too much. Uh. I
started my summer job.
Um. I had to carry my
dad up the stairs again.
You know what's funny?
When... when he drinks.
which is basically every night.
he uses this Phillies Cup.
Like. this plastic Phillies
giveaway cup he's had forever.
And he used to only
drink iced tea out of it.
And because he's using
that cup. I guess he thinks
maybe I don't know what's
really in there or something.
which is so incredibly stupid.
Have you talked
to him about that?
Using a different cup?
His drinking.
And you always having
to take care of him.
I'm gonna wait until
after sentencing.
Remind me when that is again.
Next Wednesday. 9 a.m.
Sara flies in this afternoon.
Oh.
And I know the family
impact statement
is going to come up again.
Have you decided what
you're gonna do yet?
Okay. um...
What scares you the most?
I... I guess...
I guess that if I
don't say anything.
I'm abandoning my brother.
throwing away the key. you know?
He's not gonna get
any better in there.
E-Even when he was getting
treatment out here.
seeing his therapist. taking
his meds. he still struggled.
I remember when he
played lacrosse.
Dad suddenly got this idea.
I don't know. maybe
he read it somewhere
that being on a team. the
stimulation of the game.
might be good for Ethan.
No one passed him the ball.
He freaked out. He...
totally lost it.
He ran off the field.
threw a rock through
someone's car window.
We looked for him for hours.
Where was he?
Dad found him asleep
at Maddox Field.
Curled up on the
bench in the dugout.
And if you do give a statement?
What scares you about that?
I'm scared
he'll be released.
Soon.
And that... uh. that scares
me more than anything.
Hey. boss.
-Last slice?
-No. No. thanks.
-Just saying. I'm leaving it here.
-Hey. do me a favor.
Will you round up everybody
for a status meeting. please?
Copy that. boss.
Yeah.
Hey.
Uh. boss wants a status update.
Okay.
♪
Sweet as a cake ♪
♪ Let me say. apologize ♪
-Lizzie.
-♪ For going and taking your time ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm a... ♪ - Lizzie.
-Lizzie. Lizzie. Lizzie. Lizzie.
-Oh. my God!
-Jesus.
-Jesus Christ.
Wh... Status
meeting downstairs.
Okay.
Maybe don't scare the
shit out of me next time.
Alright. everyone.
let's round robin.
-Lizzie?
-Uh. analysts tagged 12 Ring cams
that show cars within a one-mile
radius of Nance's house.
So. we're working with. um.
Marcus Hook PD right now
to match 'em to homeowners
to see what's out of place.
Okay. Aleah. what about you?
-Anything on the kid?
-None of it's good.
-Yeah.
-As of March. he'd been living
full-time with his
grandmother. Sally Moyer.
in Broomall after Children
and Youth Services
deemed the parents unfit.
What about the welfare reports?
CYS visited the house
on four occasions
over the past two years.
Mostly ChildLine tips
indicating neglect and drug use.
Sam showed up at a neighbor's
house asking for food.
Sam was repeatedly left
at home all by himself.
How'd he end up back
with the parents?
Well. the grandmother was
diagnosed with dementia
and admitted to a
memory care facility.
Derek and Joanne passed
a series of drug tests
and CYS returned Sam.
Looks like he'd only
been there a few weeks.
The kid wasn't even supposed
to be at the house last night?
-No.
-Jesus Christ.
Can I ask a question?
Lizzie. you don't have to raise
your hand to ask a question.
Right. Um. no. I just...
I don't understand
why you take the kid at all.
I think you're following
the wrong trail here.
Whoever is hitting these houses.
we find them. we find the boy.
They're primarily going
after the Dark Hearts.
-Why don't you jump in here?
-Alright.
Jayson Wilkes. Delaware
County Chapter President.
He was handpicked
by Perry Dorazo.
one of the 12 National Leaders who make
up what's known as the Mother Club.
They oversee all
gang operations.
Dorazo found Jayson
as a wayward teenager.
He took him under his
wing. championed his rise.
And the rumor was that Perry
murdered the previous
Delco president.
Butch Hampton. to ensure
Jayson would assume control.
Under Jayson's leadership.
the Dark Hearts have thrived.
Used to be they trafficked
in heroin and cocaine.
But when heroin users started
chasing a different high.
they brought in fentanyl.
And now. they're the
second largest traffickers
in the northeast.
The Dominicans control the city.
Everything goes
through Freddy Frias.
And the Dark Hearts.
the rural communities
from Lancaster County
clear through New York.
For the most part.
bikers are addicts.
partiers who sell dope
to fuel their own habits.
But the Dark Hearts
are different.
They're as strategic and close-knit
a group as I've come across.
When there's a
crack. it's sealed.
When a limb shows
weakness. they cut it off.
Which means this. to
me. doesn't make sense.
Explain "doesn't make sense."
What he's saying is that
whoever is hitting these houses
must be getting some help
from someone inside the gang.
Mm. Not just inside.
Deep inside.
-An informant?
-Mm-hmm.
-Oh. fuck.
-Lizzie. call up to Central
and ask for a meeting
with Joe Easley ASAP.
He's a walking encyclopedia of
all things East Coast bikers.
Let's get to work.
What's on your mind?
Just. if we know the
Dark Hearts got a mole...
then they do. too. and
they got their own ways
-of finding it.
-Mm.
Jay. Perry's here.
Mother Club met this morning.
They were aware of a leak. but
now they got this kid's face
on every milk carton.
telephone pole.
federal agency tracking board.
and we got this giant fuckin'
magnifying glass on us
that nobody wants.
Others have lost their
faith in your leadership.
Fuck 'em.
You have any idea what it
feels like to get sent in
to mop up your shit after all
I've done to get you here?
Huh?
I just need a little more time.
-Don't have more time...
-Look.
-You don't have any more time.
-Just give me a few days. okay?
-There is no more...
-Give me a couple more days
and I can fix everything.
Our blood and brains have been
splattered all over the walls
'cause of this crew. and
now they've got one of ours.
and it is a fucking kid.
Okay? It's a fucking kid!
And you want more time?
Fuck you. Fuck you.
Fuck you!
The buy was never made. Per.
What do you mean?
Rocco called late last night.
There was a delay on their side.
Meeting got pushed
'til the morning.
Whoever walked
out of that house.
they didn't leave with cash.
They left with 12 kilos
of unprocessed China.
China they're gonna have
to find a way to move.
And move fast.
That kinda weight. pure.
there's only one
buyer around here
-capable of moving it.
-Freddy.
Freddy's gonna want a cut.
That is not gonna be cheap.
Yeah. well.
-It's worth it.
-Alright.
I'll make a few calls. see
if I can broker something.
What else do we know so far?
Task force has been set up.
Intel is trickling in now.
-Who's in charge?
-Mm.
Field agent. His
name's Tom Brandis.
New paper pusher
from Newtown Square.
He won't be a problem.
-Mm?
-Joe Easley here to see you.
Mm! Great. Let him
know I'll be right up.
I think your instincts
are right here. Tommy.
Makes sense that the
crew would be working
with an informant
inside the gang.
Thanks.
So. what would make a gang
member turn like that?
They don't. Almost ever.
And you're not hearing
anything in BAU?
No rumblings in VCMO?
-Within the Dark Hearts?
-Yeah.
Mm-hmm. Worked a joint Task with
Mercer County last November.
Picked up a small timer on a
distro. offered him a proffer deal.
He tells us a story
about a rules violation
within the gang. very hush-hush.
-Rules violation?
-Didn't specify.
Just said that Wilkes
invited a gang member
to the Elks Lodge under
the guise of a gathering.
Once the gang member got there.
-Wilkes beat him for hours.
-Mm.
From what this guy said. by
the time he was finished.
they had the mop bits of
his brain off of the floor.
Remember. uh. gang member's name
who Wilkes attacked?
Billy something or other.
I'll call my guy down at Mercer
and get the last name for yas.
I remember telling his
daughter he was missin'.
She knew it had to be
Jayson that killed him.
-Hey. Hey. hey. don't do that.
-What?
-He likes it.
-Oh. he likes getting his head held down
and not being able to breathe?
Little shit.
Lost and found.
Wow. Bedazzles are back.
Yes. Gerry called out again.
What the fuck?
He knows I pick up
the kids at 3:30.
You go. I'll stick around.
So. how'd it go?
-How did what go?
-The date.
You said his profile pic
looked like he had an eggplant
in his underwear.
Oh. it was amazing.
We went to a nice Italian
spot. I brought him home.
And just when he was
about to go down on me.
my uncle sprang out of the
closet like a jack-in-the-box
-and beat the shit out of him.
-Oh. my God.
-Are you serious?
-Yeah.
You really need to get the
hell out of that situation.
You say it like I
don't already know.
You know. my mom makes
the best baked ziti.
You're more than welcome to
join us. crash on our couch.
Or not. that's cool. Cool. cool.
Shit. I gotta get back
to the freak farm.
-You sure you can cover?
-Bitch. please. I got you.
Watch him.
Can I go outside and
pet Gertie again?
Yeah. Yeah. sure.
Ah-ah-ah. backpacks go
on hooks. not on floors.
Stop acting like
a baby. fart-face.
-Okay. Okay.
-No!
Ah-ah-ah.
Hey. How was school?
Dad. a boy has a
crush on Harper.
No. he doesn't.
Shut up. Wyatt!
Max Selby says she's the
prettiest girl in school.
-She is.
-She can do better than Max Selby.
I see Harper kissing in a tree!
-K-I-S-S-I-N-G!
-Oh. my God. shut up. Wyatt. shut up!
Who's that?
Oh. that's. uh. Sam.
He's a friend of
mine from work's son.
-Sam?
-Um...
You remember Dale? Dale Larson?
Sam rhymes with "ham."
No. I don't remember
Dale Larson.
Yeah. he... he asked if I could
look after him for a little while.
Define a little while.
Well. Dale's m-mother
is really sick.
and so he had to
head down to Dover.
And he couldn't
ask somebody else?
He. you know. trusts me. so.
Well. that's his first problem.
How long's he
gonna be here for?
Not long. A couple of days.
Um. she... it's like. she's...
imminent. is how Dale
described it to me.
Um. uh. Hey. Harp?
Could you. uh. take Wyatt
outside and go say hi?
-Sure. Come on.
-Thanks.
-Slow down!
-I'm sorry about this.
I know you got enough
on your plate as it is.
You seriously need new friends.
I know where
they're keeping Sam.
He's way out in the woods
in the middle of nowhere.
For Christ's sakes!
I'm sorry. Miss
Evelyn. Miss Pearl.
but we... we don't accept
unscreened calls on this line.
But he's in trouble.
Brandis. you have to...
Yes. we're very well aware
that Sam's in trouble.
and we appreciate the
reminder from the beyond.
-Bye now.
-Same crystal baller again?
Yeah. Hey. Lizzie. Lizzie?
She's probably listening
to Gwen Stefani.
Hey!
-Snickerdoodle!
-What the hell is it?!
I thought we assigned an
analyst to vet the tip line.
-We did!
-Okay. I've had four calls come through
from the same psychic already.
Can you make sure
that only vetted tips
come through to us. please?
Copy. Cut it out. asshole!
FYI. there's a mouse
in the bathroom.
-A mouse?
-Mice.
There's tiny shits everywhere.
Congratulations. you're
in charge of the tip line.
Anything promising
comes through.
reach out to me ASAP.
-Where you going?
-Uh. I got... I got a family thing.
Night. boss.
Here. try these on.
Will I still get my toy?
-What toy is that?
-For finishing Reading Club.
My mom said if I finished.
she would buy me
a Batman Lego set.
Ah. you're gonna have to talk
to your mom about that one.
Can you maybe call her and
ask? Her name's Joanne.
-Joanne?
-Joanne Nance.
Is your dad's name Derek?
Mm-hmm.
Do you know my
parents like Robbie?
I used to. Yeah.
Can I go play now?
-Maeve.
-Hm?
Can I go play now?
Uh. yeah. Yeah. go ahead.
-Hey. babe. You alright?
-Yeah.
What's Jay saying
about all this?
Not much.
It's the same crew. right?
I mean. it's the
same guys that the...
-Hey.
-Yo.
I spoke to Freddy. he's
willing to meet us tomorrow.
So far. he hadn't heard anyone
looking to move that kind of weight.
So. who from our side
knows the drugs didn't
travel last night?
Mm.
Right now. just
Breaker and Shane.
Alright. keep it that way.
Let the rest of the club believe
that we're not looking
for the drugs anymore.
They're gone. as far as
they're concerned. okay?
That way. if someone's
inclined to move 'em.
they'll see an opening...
and we'll be waiting
for the fucker.
Ah. here's Bishop.
-Go greet him.
-Mm.
-I'll meet you.
-Alright.
Hey. D.
Hey.
How you been?
Every day is champagne
and strawberries.
-You look good.
-Mm-hmm.
What you doin' later?
Uh. well. it depends
on who's askin'.
Me. I'm askin'.
Well. in that case. um...
I gotta scrub my toilets.
Get the fuck off me. man.
You got any hot sauce. Em?
-I'm the weirdo who eats pizza with Cholula.
-Yeah. um. top shelf.
-I'll just... yeah.
-Ah. love it.
-Here you go.
-Thank you.
Hello?
It's me.
-We're home.
-Hey.
Uh. is Matt here?
I'll be right there. Tommy.
I'm going full Garfield on
this pizza at the moment.
Alright. I'm gonna take this
stuff up to the bedroom.
then I'm gonna make the crib up.
-Hey.
Hi. Oh.
Hey.
-Is Andy not... I thought he...
-Andy's gonna fly in on Thursday.
-Oh.
-He had a...
a second interview with a firm.
Hey.
-Yeah.
-Can I hold him?
Yeah. Yeah.
Uh. you want to sit down?
Uh. mm-hmm.
Come here. baby. Okay.
Hey.
Okay.
-Okay.
-Hello. Hello.
-You got him.
-You miss me? I missed you.
Be warned. he's gassy.
-Okay.
-Now. I'm gonna pour myself
a bucket of wine. Hey. Matt.
Hey. sweetheart.
How's life in Chicago?
Be much better when this
nightmare's finally over.
Mm-hmm. I know.
What are we doing
with the kid?
-I don't know yet.
-He's all over the news.
Radio mentioned his
name three times
-on my way back to you.
-Maybe we...
just drop him somewhere.
like a park...
Drop him? The
minute we drop him.
he's leading cops
back to your house.
Back to us.
We're not just... Droppin' him.
Let's just get the money...
and then we'll figure out
what to do with the kid.
Alright?
More crab fries?
-Kitchen's gonna close.
-No. thanks.
Yes. please.
I'll bring yous
one more basket.
Hey. Hey!
Phone's going off.
Not comin'.
Not comin'?
Let's go.
Come on.
Finally asleep.
Atta girl.
God. with teething.
he's just been impossible
to get down lately.
Matt. you wanna start. or?
Yeah. sure. I'll...
I'll jump in here.
Your father and I thought it
would be good for all of us
to sit down and walk
through what to expect
at sentencing on Wednesday.
Ethan has pled guilty to
murder in the third degree.
which has a maximum
sentence of 15 years.
Sentencing itself will be
fairly straightforward.
Have any of you seen your
brother since it happened?
I have. yeah.
I've... I've been to
visit Ethan a few times.
Alright. well. to
prepare you both.
because you haven't seen Ethan.
he looks quite different.
His hair is very short now.
He's thinner.
It will be a bit of a
shock seeing him again.
At first.
It's good that you'll
have each other.
-Mm.
-The judge will have some business to talk through.
and then he'll ask if there is
a statement from the family.
I don't know if
you've given that
-any more thought.
-We have discussed.
-We're not gonna...
-I think I'd like to say...
...something.
I thought... I thought we agreed
we... we weren't gonna
make a statement.
-I don't remember agreeing.
-Yeah. last time we all spoke.
-No. I said... I said I wasn't sure.
-Dad. you remember.
-We agreed.
-I said that I would think about it.
What exactly do
you plan on saying?
I don't know.
I haven't. like.
written it out yet.
But it would be aimed at what?
Just. um...
telling the judge a little
bit about how we grew up.
Ethan and I before we were
adopted by Mom and Dad.
And maybe that...
I don't think he's gonna
get the help he needs
from inside of a prison.
Yeah... I don't... I don't
even know what to say.
-Relax. Sara.
-This. uh. impact statement.
depending on how persuasive
Emily is. of course.
uh. is something the
judge would consider
when determining
Ethan's sentence?
As I mentioned to your
father. Judge Adams will...
will take what you all
have to say very seriously.
-Jesus fucking Christ.
-Calm down. Sara.
You're telling me there's a
chance Ethan could be released
-in five years. is that what you're telling me?
-Let's not get all worked up.
-Tom's right. he may not...
-I'm not getting worked up.
-The judge may not...
-Who's getting worked up? I'm...
Sara.
I'm asking a question.
What's wrong with
a fucking question?
Something catastrophic has
happened to our family.
Our mother was murdered.
-By her brother.
-Don't say it like that.
-Say it like what?
-Don't do that.
He had a psychiatric disorder.
and he was off his meds
-because of COVID.
-Yeah. he threw Mom down the stairs.
He broke her neck.
How'd you feel?
Dad. how do you...
how do you feel
about the idea
that in five years.
Ethan could be walking
through that door...
moving into the bedroom upstairs
and eating dinner at this
table after killing your wife?
My mother.
She was my mother too.
What? What'd you say?
-I didn't hear what you just said.
-She was my mother. too.
Uh...
Don't do that. goddamn it!
You still haven't
answered my question.
Maybe I should just step out.
Sit down. Matt.
When I was a priest. I had. uh.
some stock answer
for that question.
Yeah. it's easy to
talk about forgiveness
when it's not your loss.
I miss your mother.
I miss my son.
There's not a day that goes
by when I don't wake up
and think for a minute.
"That didn't happen.
That couldn't possibly
have happened."
Not to us. we were so...
But I did.
As for forgiveness and mercy.
Sara. God. I don't know.
I've prayed for an answer.
some kind of guidance.
and all I've gotten
in return is silence.
I'm lost.
Thanks for coming. Matt.
I'm gonna go find your sister.
Oh. Jesus Christ.
Sam.
-Sam.
-Hm?
-What?
-Shh. Come on.
-There you go.
-Where are we going?
We're gonna go get your present
for finishing Reading Club.
Mind if I bum one?
Yeah.
-Grazie. Snickerdoodle.
-Okay. can you just stop
with the whole "Snickerdoodle"?
It's... it was
literally my Yahoo email
-in. like. 2012.
-Phew.
Mine was. um.
DJGrassanova@yahoo.com.
DJ Grassanova?
I deejayed to pay my
way through college.
I worked the Catholic grade
school mixer tour for a few years.
Merion Mercy down
to Villa Maria.
All the rich Main Line kids.
I even had. like. a little...
like a routine I'd do. you know.
A routine?
-Yeah.
-What was the routine?
I can't remember.
Stover. it was. uh.
"Ladies and gentlemen.
welcome to the St. Monica
"seventh and eighth
grade mixer tour.
"Before we get
started. a few rules.
"No straddlin'. bendin'.
"grindin'. freakin'. twerkin'.
"Keep both feet on the floor.
Hands on shoulders and waist.
"Mosh pits and crowd surfing
are strictly prohibited.
"And if you're gonna PDA.
do it somewhere the priests
"and the nuns won't see yous.
"I'll be your host this evening
"with an all-request final hour.
DJ Grassanova!"
-Wow.
-Mm.
What was on your playlist?
It depend... I mean. you
gotta read the crowd.
Oh. okay. so there's.
like. this science
-behind being DJ Grassanova.
-Of course.
-Okay.
-If it's a feeder mixer.
you got kids from all
different schools.
Everyone's kind of nervous
hiding in their corners.
You gotta ease things in. right?
Something... something classic.
Like. uh. Calvin
Harris' "Summer."
But if everyone knows each other
and they're looking to grind...
-Grind? That's disgusting.
-...then I'm going straight in with Flo Rida's...
♪ Whistle baby. whistle
baby. let me know ♪
-Do you miss it?
-Being a DJ?
-Yeah.
-Every fuckin' day.
See that store? I
want you to go inside
and find that Batman
toy you wanted.
What are you gonna do?
I'm just gonna make a quick call
and then I'll be right in. okay?
Go ahead.
911. what's your emergency?
Hi. I'm at the Val-U-Corner
out on Boot Road.
I think I just saw that missing
kid you're all looking for.
-Yeah. This one?
-That one.
Tipline. this is Aleah.
Where?
Hey. possible
sighting of Sam Nance.
We gotta go.
Hey. Aleah. What's up?
Tipline reported a
sighting of Sam Nance.
Where?
Shopping center
out on Boot Road.
Y-You got a confirmation?
Clothing description
matches what we have.
They're locking the place down
and setting up checkpoints
at the exits.
-Holy shit.
-Maeve.
What...
What the...
How'd you get back in here?
I was scared 'cause
you weren't there.
Fuck.
Just climb back here.
Just get in there
and stay quiet.
-What?
-Hurry. Sam. Now. go. come on!
Now. hurry.
-It's really dark in here.
-I know. I'm sorry.
It's just for a minute. okay?
We'll go check inside.
I'm gonna go make sure
the exits are locked down.
Hey. Hey.
Where's Sam?
Harp. where is he?
Pull up.
Pull forward.
License. registration.
Open your trunk. please.
Boss.
Hey. bring me up to
speed. I have the SAC
standing by for a full report.
Anonymous 911 reported seeing
Sam at the Val-U-Corner.
Okay. what about
exterior cameras?
-We have anything...
-Nothing outside.
-Inside only. and above the registers.
-Okay.
-Fuck off. Robbie.
-Pull up. Keep coming.
Next car. please
open your trunk.
Yep. they can go.
Yeah. this one's good.
Alright. next car.
License and
registration. please.
What's all this about?
Missing child. Where
are you coming from?
KJ's. I'm the manager there.
-Open your trunk. please.
-Out of curiosity.
what the kid look like?
-Were you working tonight?
-Yeah. yeah. yeah.
I'm only asking 'cause there was
a kid inside who seemed lost.
Recently?
Yeah. just like
five minutes ago.
Have the FBI respond over
here. Got a lady here
who thinks she might have
seen the kid inside of KJ's.
10-4.
Okay. Okay. which car?
-This is the one.
-This one?
Hi. You see a boy?
-How old?
-Like. seven? Eight?
Was he by himself?
He's probably
still in there now.
Alright. park your
car and come with me.
License and registration.
Alright. right over here.
So. do any of these kids look
like the one you saw earlier?
That one.
Alright. no. You
got her information?
It's a bum tip. Let 'em go.
Alright. y'all are free to go.
Yo. Jay. Cops ID'ed that
body from their crew.
Name's Kenny Pollard.
Per.
Can I help... oh. Jesus!
Oh. God!
Please!
-Hey.
-Hey. did she come home yet?
No. Dad. we really need to discuss
Emily making this statement.
-Yeah. I'll... I'll talk to you later.
-You can't just keep...
Hey. sweetheart.
Come on. let's go home.
What have you done to us?
Do you want subtitles for any video?
-=[ ai.OpenSubtitles.com ]=-